<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Artificer</title>
	<release-date>TBA</release-date>
	<website>http://www.dtsoftworks.co.uk/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam</name>
			<link>http://www.steampowered.com/</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>
	
	<prices>			
		<price>
			<currency>GBP</currency>
			<value>-</value>
		</price>
	</prices>

	<description>
	 Artificer is a MOBA-style arena team-based game where being a team player and tactics is just as important as combat skills.
	 Each player takes the role of an artificer/pilot within a team. Ships are constructed of modular pieces that are fully
	 customizable for players. 

	 You may expend materials in storage or currency to either purchase new ship builds or create your unique starcraft using
	 the drag and drop ship editor in game. As well as building ships you may explore procedurally generated space maps, 
	 battle and conquer both enemy NPCs and players and gather resources from the enviroment to support your team.
	</description>
	
	<history>
	Artificer is based on a project created in 2014 named Eclipse created in C++ and Direct3D9 by a university student in their
	room within halls accomodation. A studio was eventually founded to support development of Artificer in July 2015
	with the intention of modernizing classic space shooter games.
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>Reminiscent of classic top-down sci-fi shooters.</feature>
		<feature>Fast paced combat arenas with a multitude of arena types.</feature>
		<feature>Build your own ships from scratch or a template within the in-game editor.</feature>
        <feature>Gain new ship component technology to upgrade and build better ships.</feature>
        <feature>Online and LAN multiplayer matches.</feature>
		<feature>The universe is alive with NPC populated space.</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>DTDigital Steam Greenlight Trailer</name>
			<youtube>RTqRrb2m-Ro</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<additionals>
        <additional>
            <title>Art Assets</title>
            <description>Skorpio's art used to build ships within demo.</description>
            <link>http://opengameart.org/users/skorpio</link>
        </additional>
	</additionals>
	
	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Daryl Boam</person>
			<role>Developer</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>

    <analytics>UA-64289722-2</analytics>
</game>